Guide to the McCann-Erickson Audiovisual Collection, 1980s-1990s and undated RL.00863
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Original Videotapes, 1980s-1990s, 49 boxes
  - 204. What In the World Will They Think of Next?, Presentation for Interpublic Board Meeting by Barry Day. 1983. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Ambre Solaire: Beautiful (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - British Airways: Hong Kong (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - Hamlet Cigars: Rubik's Cube (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - Shell: Tempest (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - Anti-Smoking PSA: Ashtray (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - National Light Bulbs: Fruit (Japan) (Box 14)
    - Heinz: Clap for It (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - Fiat: Interviewer (Brazil) (Box 14)
    - Sole Bianco: Demonstration (Italy) (Box 14)
    - Johnson & Johnson: Shampoo (Brazil) (Box 14)
    - Visa: Presenter (Spain) (Box 14)
    - Bank of Sao Paulo: Chaplin (Brazil) (Box 14)
    - Ali Coffee: Gone with the Wind (Norway) (Box 14)
    - Pontin's holidays: Esther Wiliams (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - Baby Pants: The Ballet (France) (Box 14)
    - French Wine: Smile (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - Gauloises cigarettes: Market (Germany) (Box 14)
    - Newspaper: Politics (Norway) (Box 14)
    - Trygg-Hansa Insurance: Wedding (Sweden) (Box 14)
    - Blaupunkt car radio: Feelings (Sweden) (Box 14)
    - Jane More clothing: Fountain (Japan) (Box 14)
    - Benson & Hedges: Salvage (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - John Smith's (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - John Smith's: Bunny Wunnies (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - John Smith's: Dog Tricks (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - Summary montage (Box 14)
  - 205. Barry Day, What Is A Creative Director?. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 14)
    [See also Tape 167. Advice on becoming a Creative Director; dealing with being in management and being under it as well.]
  - 206. Barry Day Interviews Judith Daniels for Women at Work Presentation. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 14)
    [See also Tapes 201, 207. New women stereotype--the business woman; household wife/bungling husband--less so now; women often still portrayed as gullible, needy of help; catering to women who work outside the home to the exclusion of the full-time homemaker; don't have to associate women with their jobs--it doesn't matter if they work or not; using the shopping center as an educational extension--no more fashion shows, women want information; time savers are very important for working women; don't have to polarize advertisements--glamor does not have to be in the office; men's reactions to the rising successes of women.]
  - 207. Barry Day Interviews Kate Rand-Lloyd for Women at Work Presentation. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 14)
    [See also tapes 201, 206. Know your target audience. Working women: 80% are in dead end, low status jobs; 20% are career oriented, professional/managerial jobs, these latter are vocal about what they like/don't like, and enjoy androgynous advertising. What is the role of fantasy in career women advertising? The female dream is not the male dream in a dress. Advertising doesn't do any favors to housewives by perpetuating the fantasy of homemaking as wonderful and lasting forever. Many housewives will be headed back to the workforce, and they need to be prepared.]
  - 208. Off Air Dub Channel 10 Interviews Barry Day, The Working Woman (Australia). 1980. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 14)
  - [209: Missing] (Box 14)
    [See also tapes 427, 429, 430, 431, 432, 433]
  - 210. World of Difference Presentation, Barry Day. 1981. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 45:00
    - Nugget shoe polish (Spain) (Box 14)
    - Outline low-fat spread: Zip (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - Preference L'Oreal: I'm Worth It (Box 14)
    - Sprite Light: 3 Models (Switzerland) (Box 14)
    - Ricore/Nestlé coffee: Coffee Closeups (Portugal) (Box 14)
    - Ambiare Air Freshener: Flowers (Spain) (Box 14)
    - Food montage (Box 14)
    - Proctor-Silex lightweight iron: Rabbit (Box 14)
    - Christie soft cookies: Quiet Cookies (Canada) (Box 14)
    - Novamura wallpaper: Dresses (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - Band-Aid: Swimming Club (Japan) (Box 14)
    - Philishave electric shaver: Hospital (Canada) (Box 14)
    - GM Commodore: Car as Plane (Brazil) (Box 14)
    - T.A.A.: Subjective Plane (Australia) (Box 14)
    - Ontario Pork: Georgian Bay (Canada) (Box 14)
    - Viking Line cruises: Ship (Finland) (Box 14)
    - GM Kadett/Opel: Photo Session (South Africa) (Box 14)
    - Esso: Energy Crisis (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - Kodak Ektra Cameras: Beach (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - Coca-Cola: Bottles (Germany) (Box 14)
    - New York Times: Globe (Box 14)
    - Telephone: Family Holiday (Italy) (Box 14)
    - Levi's: Body Talk (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - Body Mist: Railway Gossip (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - Inspire: Escalator (Germany) (Box 14)
    - L'Oreal: L'Oreal Girls (Australia) (Box 14)
    - La Roche Aux Fees: Child's World (France) (Box 14)
    - Pabst Blue Ribbon Beer: Bartender (Box 14)
    - Christie soft cookies: Birthday Party (Canada) (Box 14)
    - Coca-Cola: Sisters (Box 14)
    - Deutsche Bundesbahn: Steward (Germany) (Box 14)
    - Frigo de Do popsicle: Fickle Finger (Spain) (Box 14)
    - Lakerol candy: Bjorn Borg (Sweden) (Box 14)
    - Tab soft drink: Girl on Beach (Box 14)
    - Martini: Waitress (U.K.) (Box 14)
    - Coca-Cola: Mean Joe Greene (Box 14)
    - United Way: Woman in Car (Box 14)
    - Your Milan: Child Art (Italy) (Box 14)
    - Easter Seals: Keith (Canada) (Box 14)
    - Final montage (Box 14)
  - 211. Barry Day: Potato Salad, Guy Atchley, Family Symptoms, Tu-Tu. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 2:30
    - Hellman's: Potato Salad (Box 14)
    - Live at Five: Guy Atchley (Box 14)
    - Triaminic: Family Symptoms (Box 14)
    - Coke: Tu-Tu (Box 14)
  - 212. Bartles & Jaymes: Liberty, Disco, Chicken Soup, On Ice/NY, Friendly City, Tavern Sign. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 3:00
    - Liberty (Box 14)
    - Disco (Box 14)
    - Chicken Soup (Box 14)
    - On Ice/N.Y. (Box 14)
    - Friendly City (Box 14)
    - Tavern Sign (Box 14)
  - 213. Four 1985 Bartles & Jaymes TV Commercials (Sitting on Steps). 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 14)
    [Product-launching commercials. We've decided to make wine coolers. We've picked a bottle, we're ready to print labels but we have no names. Thanks for suggestions--It's now Bartles & Jaymes. We only make the best.]
  - 214. Labatt Ontario Breweries, Blue Light. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Beer Talk (Box 14)
    - Beer Chat (Box 14)
    - Beer Banter (Box 14)
  - 215. Harrod & Mirling Santa Fe/California Cooler. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Tropical Natural (Box 14)
    - The Fizz Natural (Box 14)
    - Peach Natural (Box 14)
    - Citrus Natural (Box 14)
    - Orange Natural (Box 14)
  - 216. Guinness Genius Campaign, From UK. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Nature Scenes (Box 14)
    - City Night (Box 14)
    - Bar Scene (Box 14)
    - ESP (Box 14)
  - 217. Martini: Bianco 60 second, Bianco Swiss/French, Bianco Swiss/German. 1986. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 15)
    - Bianco (Box 15)
    - Bianco (Swiss/French) (Box 15)
    - Bianco (Swiss/German) (Box 15)
  - 218. Martini (Montage). 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 2:00 (Box 15)
  - 219. Guinness: Natural Genius and Pure Genius. 1985. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 15)
  - 220. Martini International. 1986. Umatic. PAL. TRT: Unknown. (Box 15)
  - 221. Martini & Rossi: Greek Fiesta, Greek Fiesta, Venice, Venice. 1984. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 3:00
    - Greek Fiesta (Box 15)
    - Greek Fiesta (Box 15)
    - Venice (Box 15)
    - Venice (Box 15)
  - 222. Martini Rosso Montage (International). 1985. Umatic. PAL. TRT: Unknown. (Box 15)
  - 223. Martini & Rossi SA, Label. 1986. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 15)
  - 224. Martini Rosso Montage (UK). 1985. Umatic. PAL. TRT: Unknown. (Box 15)
  - 225. Tuborg Experimental Commercial (London). 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 15)
  - 226. Tuborg Human Train. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 1:00 (Box 15)
  - 227. John Smith's Yorkshire Bitter (Arkwright) Finished Films. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Art of Conversation (Box 15)
    - Tchaikovsky (Box 15)
    - Art Lovers (Box 15)
    - Average May Fly (Box 15)
    - Appearances (Box 15)
    - Cannes (Box 15)
    - C'est Bon (Box 15)
    - Bunny-wunnies (Box 15)
    - Book Lovers (Box 15)
    - Tough Act (Box 15)
    - Romantics (Box 15)
    - Led Astray (Box 15)
    - Memories (Box 15)
    - Fitness Fanatics (Box 15)
    - Song and Dance (Box 15)
  - 228. Interpublic Group, Coca-Cola, Stopover. 1984. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 1:06
    - Coca-Cola: Stopover (Argentina) (Box 15)
  - 229. Buy the World, Cosby--History, Cosby--The Grand Opening, Taste For You II, Coke Is It Premiere. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 4:00
    - New Coke: Buy the World a Coke (Box 15)
    - New Coke: Cosby--History (Box 15)
    - New Coke: Cosby--Grand Opening (Box 15)
    - New Coke: Taste for You II (Box 15)
    - New Coke: Coke Is It! Premiere (Box 15)
  - 230. McCann/Tokyo, Coke, Barry Hill as Creative Director. 1983. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Coca-Cola: Concert (Tokyo) (Box 15)
  - [231: Missing] (Box 15)
  - 232. Coca-Cola Youth Oriented Commercials. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Sears/Men's Store: Courduroy TMC (Box 15)
    - Marriott: Tough Guys (Box 15)
    - Burrell Afro Sheen: Broadway (Box 15)
    - McDonald's: Fall Up (Box 15)
    - Highland Appliance (Box 15)
    - Buick (Box 15)
    - Bubblicious (Box 15)
    - Levi's Boots (Box 15)
    - Clairol (Box 15)
    - Posner (Box 15)
    - Astroworld Greezed Lightnin (Box 15)
    - Gordon's Jewlers Disco (Box 15)
    - Italian Swiss Colony Wines (Box 15)
    - Six Flags (Box 15)
    - Laura Scudders: Clacking Teeth (Box 15)
    - Laura Scudders: Ball Game (Box 15)
    - Straw Hat Restaurant Corp. (Box 15)
    - San Francisco Public Library (Box 15)
    - San Francisco Police Department (Box 15)
    - T.J. Swann: Stepping Out (Box 15)
    - T.J. Swann: All the Way with T.J. (Box 15)
    - Annie Green Springs: Barn (Box 15)
    - United Vitners: Barbecue (Box 15)
    - Varathane: Roller King (Box 15)
    - Capri-Sonne (Box 15)
    - Snickers (Box 15)
    - Vademecum Mouth Wash (Box 15)
    - Lois Jeans (Box 15)
    - Mars Candy (Box 15)
    - Wrigley (Box 15)
    - Happy Mentos Mint (Box 15)
    - Pepsi Cola (Box 15)
    - Sinalco (Box 15)
    - Janie D (Box 15)
    - Nesquick: Nougat (Box 15)
    - Balin Discount Train Ticket (Box 15)
    - AKO Toffy Candy (Box 15)
    - HALS (Box 15)
    - Toffel Crisp (Box 15)
    - Cervenza Andes (Box 15)
    - Chiclets (Box 15)
    - Seven Up (Box 15)
    - Far West (Box 15)
    - Kansas (Box 15)
    - Jockey Club (Box 15)
    - Lee (Box 15)
    - Juicy Fruit (Box 15)
    - Magnolia Ice Cream (Box 15)
    - Nescafé (Box 15)
    - Close-Up (Box 15)
    - Clearasil (Box 15)
    - Dial Soap (Box 15)
    - Newtex Napkins (Box 15)
    - Anson Emporium (Box 15)
    - Ford Escort (Box 15)
    - Swift's Processed Meats (Box 15)
  - 233. Coke/Hi-C/Fanta/Kin (Korea Version). Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Truck Party (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Beach Can (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Candle (Box 16)
    - Hi-C: Bicycle (Box 16)
    - Hi-C: The Keuk-Kwon (Box 16)
    - Hi-C: '86 Orange (Box 16)
    - Fanta: Disney Pop Concert (Box 16)
    - Kin: Together with Kin (Box 16)
    - Kin: Tent (Box 16)
  - 234. Bill Cosby Spots. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - New Coke: History (Box 16)
    - New Coke: It's Better (Box 16)
    - New Coke: Grand Opening (Box 16)
    - New Coke: What Will I Say? (Box 16)
  - 235. Coca-Cola Company Commercials--Interpublic Group (Coca-Cola Bottler--Bermuda). Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Diet Coke: JFF Whitney (Box 16)
    - Diet Coke: JFF Whitney (Box 16)
    - Diet Coke: JFF Whitney (Box 16)
    - Diet Coke: Renee (Box 16)
    - Diet Coke: JFF Sax (Box 16)
    - Tab: Weird (Box 16)
    - Tab: The Only One (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola Classic: Rhythm & Blues (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola Classic: Rock (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola Classic: Country (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola Classic: Jazz/Swing (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola Classic: Rhythm & Blues (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola Classic: Rock (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola Classic: Country (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola Classic: Jazz/Jarreau (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola Classic: Rhythm & Blues (Box 16)
    - Cherry Coke: Cherry Boulevard (Box 16)
    - Fresca: The Perfect Soft Drink (Box 16)
    - Fresca: The Perfect Soft Drink (Box 16)
    - Fresca: The Perfect Soft Drink (Box 16)
    - Cherry Coke: Weightlifter/Bathtub (Box 16)
    - Cherry Coke: Painting/Magician (Box 16)
    - Cherry Coke: Popcorn/Grandma (Box 16)
    - Cherry Coke: Elevator/Punks (Box 16)
    - Cherry Coke: Weightlifter/Bathtub (Box 16)
    - Cherry Coke: Elevator/Punks (Box 16)
    - Sprite: Beach Ride (Box 16)
    - Sprite: Waterfall (Box 16)
    - Sprite: Divers (Box 16)
    - Sprite: Swings (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Good Times (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Good Times (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: City Life (Box 16)
    - Diet Cherry Coke: Cherry Boulevard (Box 16)
    - Tab: Touch Me (Box 16)
    - New Coca-Cola: Beach Wave (Box 16)
    - New Coca-Cola: Beach Wave (Box 16)
    - New Coca-Cola: Desert Island (Box 16)
    - New Coca-Cola: Horizontal Pour (Box 16)
    - New Coca-Cola: Technical Difficulties (Box 16)
    - New Coca-Cola (Max Headroom): Truck (Box 16)
    - New Coca-Cola (Max Headroom): Truck (Box 16)
    - New Coca-Cola (Max Headroom): Philip's Room (Box 16)
    - New Coca-Cola (Max Headroom): Diner (Box 16)
    - New Coca-Cola (Max Headroom): Pop Quiz (Box 16)
    - New Coca-Cola (Max Headroom): Interview (Box 16)
    - Sprite: Lymon (Box 16)
    - Sprite: Trade-In (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Taste Tease (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Breaks (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Cool Moves (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Hard Rock Café (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Hard Rock Café (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Heat of the Night (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Heat of the Night (Box 16)
  - 236. The Coca-Cola Company, Cherry Coca-Cola/Cherry Coke International. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 4:30
    - Cherry Coke: Weightlifter/Bathtub intro graphic (Box 16)
    - Cherry Coke: Popcorn/Grandma intro graphic (Box 16)
    - Cherry Coke: Painting/Magician intro graphic (Box 16)
    - Cherry Coke: Elevator/Punk intro graphic (Box 16)
    - Cherry Coke: Weightlifter/Painting/Magician/Bathtub intro graphic (Box 16)
    - Cherry Coke: Elevator/Popcorn/Grandma/Punk intro graphic (Box 16)
    - Cherry Coke: Popcorn/Grandma sustaining graphic (Box 16)
  - 237. Coca-Cola 1985. 1985. Umatic. TRT: Unknown.
    [See also Tapes 254, 255]
    - Coca-Cola: Buy the World (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Cosby--History (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Cosby--Grand Opening (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Cosby--Unemployment (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Taste for You II (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: What It Is--Product (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: What It Is--Taste (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Coke Is It--Premiere (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Coke Is It--Sports (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Light (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Other (Box 16)
  - 238. Coca-Cola USA, Coke: Max Truck, Phillips' Room. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 1:30
    - Coca-Cola: Max Truck (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Max Truck (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Phillip's Room (Box 16)
  - [239: Missing] (Box 16)
  - 240. 1986 Coke/Sprite--1st Quarter Division File Report (Philippines). 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Coca-Cola: Elana (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Laura (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Sizzle (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Omnibus (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Send in the Clowns (Box 16)
    - Pepsi-Cola: Fort Santiago (Box 16)
    - Pepsi-Cola: Jeepney (Box 16)
    - Pop Cola: Indian (Box 16)
    - Pop Cola: Drink a Pop Win a Toy promo (Box 16)
    - Sprite: Beach Ride (Box 16)
    - 7-Up: Hot City (Box 16)
    - Royal Tru-Orange: Mon Alvir/Herbert Bautista (Box 16)
    - Cheers: Lifeboat (Box 16)
    - Sarsi: Ideal Fun (Box 16)
    - Hi-C: Apple (Box 16)
    - Magnolia: Magnolia Fruit Drinks (Buko/Calamansi/Guyabano) (Box 16)
    - Kool Aid: Hide and Seek (Box 16)
    - Kool Aid: Hockey (Box 16)
    - Dole: Doubly Dole-icious (Tetra Brik) (Box 16)
    - Zesto: Fresh and Cool (Box 16)
  - [241: Missing] (Box 16)
  - 242. Coca-Cola International Pattern & Blueprint Advertising. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Song pattern (Box 16)
    - Song (Brazil) (Box 16)
    - Mean Joe Greene (USA) (Box 16)
    - Mean Joe Greene (Spain) (Box 16)
    - Mean Joe Greene/Zico (Brazil) (Box 16)
    - Mean Joe Greene/Mardona (Argentina) (Box 16)
    - Mean Joe Greene/Nywat (Thailand) (Box 16)
    - Fireworks pattern (Box 16)
    - Fireworks (Korea) (Box 16)
    - Sidewalk Café pattern (Box 16)
    - Sidewalk Café (Argentina) (Box 16)
    - Block Party pattern (Box 16)
    - Block Party (Italy) (Box 16)
    - Hottest Day pattern (Box 16)
    - Hottest Day (Germany) (Box 16)
    - Hobie Cat pattern (Box 16)
    - Hobie Cat (Mexico) (Box 16)
    - Soccermania pattern (Box 16)
    - Soccermania (Greece) (Box 16)
    - Thirsty Workers pattern (Box 16)
    - Thirsty Workers (Germany) (Box 16)
  - 243. Joe's Place--Coca-Cola. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 16)
  - 244. Coke Compliation Showreel. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Junior High (Box 16)
    - Two Girls (Box 16)
    - After School--Power (Box 16)
    - Bif's Luncheonette (Box 16)
    - Cinema Line (Box 16)
    - Older Brother (Box 16)
    - Coke Classic (Box 16)
    - Classic Moments I (Box 16)
    - Classic Moments II (Box 16)
    - It's Back--Man to Camera (Box 16)
    - Song over Movement on Coke Classic Can: Happy Days Are Here Again (Box 16)
    - Manifesto (Box 16)
    - Manifesto/Witness (Box 16)
    - Manifesto/Pumping Iron (Box 16)
    - Flyball (Box 16)
    - Bike Romance (Box 16)
    - Branding Devices (Box 16)
  - 245. Coke International: Olympic Journey (Brazil), Stopover (Argentina), Diner (Japan), On the Beach (Int'l), Sizzle (Int'l). 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Coca-Cola: Olympic Journey (Brazil) (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Stopover (Argentina) (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Diner (Japan) (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: On the Beach (International) (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Sizzle (International) (Box 16)
    - Camel Cigarettes: Raft Tent (Box 16)
    - Camel Cigarettes: Print ad montage (Box 16)
    - Marlboro: Marlboro Country (Box 16)
    - Marlboro montage (Box 16)
    - Cinzano Rosso: The World of Cinzano (Box 16)
    - Martini montage (Box 16)
  - 246. Coke International: Truck Party, Beach Can, Tennis. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Coca-Cola: Truck Party pattern (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Truck Party (Mexico) (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Truck Party (Korea) (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Beach Can pattern (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Beach Can (Germany) (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Beach Can (South Africa) (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Tennis pattern (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Tennis (Central America) (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Tennis (Austria) (Box 16)
  - 247. Coca-Cola Australia: Sprite, Coke, & Diet Coke Presentation. 1987. Umatic. PAL. TRT: Unknown.
    - Sprite: Girls (Box 16)
    - Sprite: Guys (Box 16)
    - Diet Coke: Elle/Glenn Combination (Box 16)
    - Diet Coke: Elle (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: First Fleet Departure (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: First Fleet Surfing (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: First Fleet Country (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Surfing (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Country (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: John Farnham (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Kitchen (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Boris Becker (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Buddy--Girl (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Buddy--Boy (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola theme radio: Janet (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola theme radio: Janet (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola theme radio: Rock (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola theme radio: Anita (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola theme radio: Doobies (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola theme radio: Doobies (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola theme radio: Prince (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola theme radio: Four Seasons (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola theme radio: Salad (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola theme radio: UB Quiet (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola theme radio: UB Quiet (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola theme radio: Bon Ami (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola theme radio: Bon Ami (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola theme radio: Jump (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola tactical radio: The Supremes (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola tactical radio: The Supremes (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola tactical radio: Mum & Sport (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola tactical radio: The Bingles (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola Max Headroom radio: Max Dictionary (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola Max Headroom radio: Max Rap (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola Max Headroom radio: Max Quiz (Box 16)
    - Diet Coke theme radio: Whitney (Box 16)
    - Diet Coke theme radio: Bubbles (Box 16)
    - Diet Coke theme radio: Benson (Box 16)
    - Diet Coke theme radio: Benson (Box 16)
    - Diet Coke tactical radio: Aerobatics (Box 16)
    - Diet Coke tactical radio: Girls (Box 16)
    - Diet Coke tactical radio: Beach (Box 16)
  - [248: Missing] (Box 16)
  - 249. Coca-Cola Is It! Tape No. 5. Undated. Umatic. TRT: Unknown.
    - Coca-Cola: Lost and Found Love (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Lost and Found Love (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Packing 'n Rafting (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Packing 'n Rafting (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: On the Beach (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Water Tunnel (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Water Tunnel (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Shooting Break (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Shooting Break (Box 16)
  - [250: Missing] (Box 16)
  - [251: Missing] (Box 16)
  - 252. Coca-Cola USA: Sports/Combo, Airshow/Coke Only, Tutu. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 1:30
    - Coca-Cola: Sports/Combo (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Air Show/Coke only (Box 16)
    - Coca-Cola: Tutu (Box 16)
  - 253. Coca-Cola Company: Taste Tease, Breaks, Cool Moves, Hard Rock Café, Heat of the Night. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 4:30 (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Taste Tease (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Breaks (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Cool Moves (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Hard Rock Café (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Hard Rock Café (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Heat of the Night (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Heat of the Night (Box 17)
  - 254. Coca-Cola Reformation: Buy the World, Cosby--History/Grand Opening, Unemployment, Taste for You II, What It Is, Coke Is It. 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    [See also Tapes 237, 255]
    - Coca-Cola: Buy the World (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Cosby--History (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Cosby--Grand Opening (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Cosby--Unemployment (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Taste for You II (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: What It Is--Product (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: What It Is--Taste (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Coke Is It--Premiere (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Coke Is It--Sports (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Light (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Other (Box 17)
  - 255. Coca-Cola Reformation: Buy the World, Cosby--History/Grand Opening, Unemployment, Taste for You II, What It Is, Coke Is It. 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    [See also Tapes 237, 254]
    - Coca-Cola: Buy the World (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Cosby--History (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Cosby--Grand Opening (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Cosby--Unemployment (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Taste for You II (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: What It Is--Product (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: What It Is--Taste (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Coke Is It--Premiere (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Coke Is It--Sports (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Light (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Other (Box 17)
  - 256. CBS Morning News, Barbara Lippert, Coca-Cola and Max Headroom. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    [The story behind Max Headroom: What he is; where he came from; how he helps Coke against Pepsi.]
    - Coca-Cola: Max Headroom/Catch Me (Box 17)
    - Coca-Cola: Max Headroom/Interview (Box 17)
  - 257. Coca-Cola, Newsboy/Fitness, Work Pix & Track. 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 00:30
    - New Coke: Newsboy/Fitness (Box 17)
  - 258. Coca-Cola. 1985-1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Coca-Cola: Artesano (Box 17)